Bisbee Deportation Legal Papers and Exhibits 1917-1919
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Simmons vs. El Paso and Southwestern Rail Road Depositions [Sheehan, Klein, Barry, Cahill, Quinn, Furbershaw, Lutz, Hughes, Wilder]. Acknowledgements of Service., 1919
  - Acknowledgement of Service No. 2364, by Court Reporter, 12pp, 11/11/1919 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Acknowledgement of Service No. 2364, by Court Reporter, 12pp, 10/21/1919 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Acknowledgement of Service No. 2364, by Court Reporter, 12pp, 11/11/1919 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Simmons vs. El Paso and Southwestern R.R. Depositions [Daniels, Berridge, etc.], 1917-1919
  - No. 2364 cover sheet, by Robert Gibbons, Notary Public, 1p, 11/26/1919 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Depositions No. 2364, by Court Reporter, 55pp, 11/19/1919 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Defendan't Exhibit 3. Letter to William D. Haywood from J. Cully, exhibit from deposition No. 2364, 6pp, 7/11/1917 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Defendan't Exhibit 4. Exhibit from No. 2364, 1p (Box 2, Folder 6)